ILGWU Joint Board Dress & Waistmakers' Union of Greater New York Managers' Correspondence 5780/047
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Agreements, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Agreements with McKettrick Williams, Inc., Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc., Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers Group, Inc., & United Popular Dress Manufacturers Association, Inc.
- Agreements, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Agreement with Associated Lerner Shops of America, Inc.
- Agreements, 1939-1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Agreements with Affiliated Ladies' Apparel Carriers of the Eastern Area, Inc., and New York and New England Dress Carriers' Association, Inc.
- Agreements, Implementation, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Special agreements for opening inside shop or enlarging facilities by transfer of workers from firm's contractors.
- Alonso, Luis Ricardo, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Corres. re employment in U.S.A.
- American Federation of Labor, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Speech by Julius Hochman, introducing resolution at AFL convention in Toronto to establish a Public Relations Dept.; incl. text of Toronto Star editorial.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), Committees, 1957-1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Incl. correspondence. re committees on Social Security and Civil Rights Compliance; ltrs. from George Meany & Walter Reuther.
- AFL-CIO, Civil Rights Committee (Subcommittee on Compliance), 1956-1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  I.c.w. Boris Shishkin, Al Hartnett, Herbert Hill, Emanuel Muravchik, correspondence. & newspaper clippings re controversy over Pittsburgh Courier charges (1959).
- AFL-CIO, International Affairs Department, 1958-1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  I.c.w. Irving Brown, Maida Springer, re Institute of Tailoring & Cutting (Kenya).
- American Jewish Tercentenary, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Antonini, Luigi, 1943-1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Art, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  I.c.w. Contemporary Arts & Archives of American Art.
- Associations, 1932-1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Louis Nizer ltr. re retainer; incl. correspondence. bet. Emil Schlesinger & Pennsyl­vania Dress Manufacturers Association, Inc.; also I.c.w. legislature & mayor's office re electrical costs for employers; copy of agreement bet. N.J. Dress Mfrs. & Contractors Assoc., Inc., & Popular Priced Dress Contractors Assoc., Inc.
- B, 1959-1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Birthday Anniversary, Charles S. Zimmerman, 1957-1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Incl. ltrs. of tribute from Lyndon B. Johnson, A. Philip Randolph, Harry Van Arsdale, William Fitts Ryan; journal.
- Bulletin. Dressmakers' Joint Council. (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- C, 1952-1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Central Trades and Labor Council of Greater N.Y., 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Incl. documents & correspondence. re expulsion of Joseph Tuvim.
- City of Hope, 1949-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Civil Rights, 1960-1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. NAACP Legal & Defense Fund with CSZ ltr. of resignation, George Meany, National Urban League (NYC), Commission on Intergroup Relations (NYC) & Central Labor Council; Robert J. Kennedy and Robert Wagner ltrs.
- Civil Rights, 1952-1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. National Urban League
- Communism, 1925-1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Ltrs. from Harry Edmonds (director). International House & Rose Baron (secre­tary). International Labor Defense; statement of Executive Committee of Cloakmakers' General Strike Committee (Nov. 18, 1926); texts of articles from Freiheit; The Communist Plague In Our unions (pamphlet).
- Communism. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Leaflets.
- Complaints, Workers', 1946-1955 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Constitution. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Conventions. [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Dress Jt. Bd. reports.
- Conventions. [folder 2 of 2], 1947-1953 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Courts, Mayor's Committee on, 1956-1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Negotiations. Newspaper Clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Nov. 1963-Apr. 1964.
- D, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Department Managers, 1947-1956 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Minutes of meetings; also incl. minutes of two Jt. Bd. staff meetings (1950).
- Disability and Health Plans Dept., 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Incl. minutes & reports of Eligibility Sub-committee.
- Disability and Health Plans Dept., 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Disability and Health Plans Dept., 1946-1956 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. Emil Schlesinger; statistical tables.
- Disability and Health Plans Dept., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Discrimination, N.Y. State Commission Against, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Labor Advisory Committee. Incl. correspondence., reports. Governor's Citation to Charles S. Zimmerman.
- Discrimination in Housing, National Committee Against, 1955-1961 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  I.c.w. Algernon D. Black & Frances Levenson.
- Discrimination in Housing, N.Y. State Committee on, 1949-1958 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  I.c.w. Algernon D. Black.
- Districts and Regions, 1954-1960 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  I.c.w. Martin J. Morand, E.T. Kehrer, N. Kirtzman, Angela Bambace, Harry Schindler, Frederick Siems, Ralph Roberts.
- Dress Industry, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Jan. 1940. Minutes of Conference on Dress Situation, incl. Meyer Perlstein's report on Chicago area.
- Dress Industry Data, 1949-1955 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Section Piece Work Schedules, Official Price Settlement List, Management-Engineering Report (Feb. 28, 1949), sales figures for NYC dress industry.
- Dress Industry Data, 1942-1949 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Dress Industry Data, 1937-1947 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Payroll & wage increase data; incl. Week Workers Survey (1947); news release (Feb. 18, 1946) re wage increase demand.
- Dress and Waistmakers' Union, Joint Board, NYC, 1955-1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Minutes, Bd. of Dir.
- Dubinsky, David, 1947-1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Incl. correspondence. re movement of firms to Penna.
- E, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Eastern Out-of-Town Dept., 1944-1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  I.c.w. Israel Horowitz, Antonio Crivello, Salvatore Ninfo, Harry Wander; speech by JH.
- Eastern Region, 1958-1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  I.c.w. Edward Kramer.
- Education Dept., Union, 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Incl. Mark Starr ltrs.; texts of "Ideas and Suggestions" & "Operation ILGWU Education;" minutes of N.Y. Educational Directors' meetings.
- Efficiency Management Dept., Union, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Schedule of piece-work prices for cotton dresses, prepared for the Waist and Dressmakers Jt. Bd., Phila., Pa.
- Elections, General, 1968-1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  I.c.w. Louis Stulberg, leaflets.
- Elections, General, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Elections, General, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Incl. ltr. from Jack Rosen (president), United Better Dress Mfrs. Assoc., Inc., re contributions; announcement of candidacy of E. Howard Molisani for councilman-at-large in 1963 election.
- Elections, General, 1958-1962 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Elections, Locals 9,10,22,60,89, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Leaflets, ltrs., ballots re elections for local officers; incl. Yiddish newspaper clippings.
- Elections, Locals 10,22,60,89, 1947-1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Election results for Local 22; leaflets.
- Elections, Local unions, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Incl. opposition leaflets.
- Federation of Union Representatives (F.O.U.R.), 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Finances, 1951-1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Monthly budget for Joint Board.
- Funerals, 1950-1955 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Speeches at services for Frederick Umhey, David Lvovich (Davidovich) & Leon Blum.
- General Executive Board (GEB), 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Incl. reports of Dressmakers' Jt. Council to GEB.
- GEB, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Appeal by Helen Steinberg, Local 4.
- GEB, 1949-1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Incl. general manager's reports to Jt. Bd. re GEB meetings; Union membership figures (1949-59).
- GEB, 1941-1949 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- GEB, Education Committee, 1941-1955 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  I.c.w. Hark Starr; drafts of leaflets; reports.
- GEB, Education Committee, 1941-1954 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Frederick F. Umhey & Arthur Elder, report by Fannia M. Cohn (1941- 42), minutes of meetings.
- General Manager, 1958-1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Incl. ltrs. from Sol C. Chaikin & Upton Sinclair, speech by Israel Breslow at CSZ installation; newspaper clippings re CSZ retirement.
- General Manager, 1934-1957 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Incl. ltrs. re Meyer Perlstein's retirement (Aug. 14, 1957) and Joseph Breslaw's death (July 16, 1957), Louis Boudin memo on ORT, press comments on Efficiency Clause (February 1941).
- General Manager, 1927-1940 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Incl. acceptance of nomination as general manager, leaflets.
- General Manager. [folder 1 of 2], 1950-1965 (Box 6, Folder 5a)
  Articles by JH & CSZ, incl. "Free Trade Unions in the Developing Countries" & newspaper clippings from India & Greece.
- General Manager. [folder 2 of 2], 1950-1965 (Box 6, Folder 5b)
- General Manager, 1936-1949 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Articles, by JH, incl. "The Retirement Myth" (1949), "Labor and the Public" (1943), "Dressmakers' Union Promotes Industry Planning" (1941).
- General Manager, 1936-1960 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Pamphlets by JH, incl. Industry Planning Through Collective Bargaining (1941).
- General Manager, 1935-1950 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Speeches for convention by JH.
- General Manager, 1957-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Speeches by JH, incl. his resignation & nomination of CSZ.
- General Manager, 1948-1951 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Speeches by JH.
- General Manager, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Speeches, notes for Harvard Lectures.
- General Manager, 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- General Manager, 1944-1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- General Manager, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- General Manager, 1938-1941 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- General Manager, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- General Manager, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- General Manager, 1926-1935 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- General Manager, 1933-1958 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  JH biographical material.
- H, 1958-1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Incl. ltrs. from Averell Harriman & Hubert H. Humphrey.
- Health and Welfare and Retirement Funds. [folder 1 of 2], 1944-1955 (Box 9, Folder 2a)
  Incl. texts of regulations.
- Health and Welfare and Retirement Funds. [folder 1 of 2], 1944-1955 (Box 9, Folder 2b)
- Health and Welfare Funds, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Incl. eligibility & coverage under Health Ins. Plan of Greater N.Y.
- Health and Welfare Funds, 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Ltr. to D.D. re administrative costs; statistics.
- Health and Welfare Funds, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Statistics on administrative accounts.
- Health and Welfare Funds, 1947-1951 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Incl. reports from Louis Brass; text of "Proposed General Plan for Operation of Health Fund."
- Health and Welfare Funds, 1945-1951 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Incl. minutes of Health Fund Council and Health & Welfare Fund Committee (Union).
- Health and Welfare Funds, 1947-1950 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Financial statements.
- Health and Welfare Funds, 1938-1948 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Financial reports.
- Health Fund, 1952-1957 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Firms delinquent in Fund payments; legal correspondence; reports of settlements.
- Health Fund, Accounting Dept., 1947-1951 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- History and Structure, 1941-1953 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Incl. "Our Union's History" (anon.).
- History and Structure, 1909-1934 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Incl. organizational chart, chronological record of Waistmakers' Strike.
- History and Structure, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Incl. "Manifesto To All Dressmakers" (Local 22), leaflets.
- History and Structure, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Incl. "Facts About the Cloak Strike;" advance copy of "The Limits of Unemploy­ment Insurance" by John R. Commons (1924); "Final Recommendations" by Governor's Advisory Commission; "Needle Trades Revolt Against Communism" by Louis Stark; report to Local 22 members by Julius Portnoy; manager's report on scab work in Boston.
- Julius Hochman, 1943-1957 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Personal correspondence.
- Julius Hochman, 1941-1946 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Articles by Eugene Lyons and Martha Dodson re JH.
- Julius Hochman, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Corres. re distribution of article, "Labor & the Public."
- Hughes -Ashberry, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Statement to N.Y. State Senate & Assembly Labor Committees re Hughes-Ashberry bill by Wilbur Daniels.
- Impartial Chairman (I.c.), 1936-1956 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Decisions by the I.c. (Harry Uviller).
- Impartial Chairman, 1940-1955 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Impartial Chairman, 1936-1945 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Minutes & reports of Administrative Board of I.c. office.
- Institute of International Labor Research, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Incl. ltrs. & reports re Centro de Estudios y Documentacion Sociales & Panoramas.
- InterAmerican Textile, Leather and Garment Workers Federation (ITLGWF), 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  I.c.w. Carlos Bedoya & text of resolution on textile & clothing imports & exports.
- ITLGWF, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  I.c.w. Carlos Bedoya, report to III Congress of ITLGWF by ILGWU, also reports by Saby Nehama, Charles S. Zimmerman and C. Bedoya; newspaper clippings.
- Intergroup Relations Commission. [folder 1 of 2], 1956-1962 (Box 11, Folder 8a)
  Incl. reports & news releases.
- Intergroup Relations Commission. [folder 1 of 2], 1956-1962 (Box 11, Folder 8b)
- International Labor Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Corres. w. American Institute for Free Labor Development, Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores, Federacion Obrera Nacional de la Industria del Vestido y Afines.
- International Labor Affairs, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- International Labor Organization, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Incl. brief history of Union & of Local 60.
- ILGWU, Cooperative Houses, 1962-1972 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- International Rescue Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Leo Cherne, Max Weinrich & Lucienne & Steve Dimitroff; also correspondence. re Diego Rivera murals & panels.
- Investigations, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- J, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 3a)
- Jewish Daily Forward, 1950-1952 (Box 12, Folder 3b)
  Hearing & award re wage dispute bet. Forward & its writers.
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1968-1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Incl. correspondence. re emigration of Jews from Poland.
- Jewish Labor Committee. [folder 1 of 2], 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Jewish Labor Committee. [folder 2 of 2], 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1949-1952 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Incl. memorandum re field work, minutes and Statement of Principles of JLC Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism,
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1945-1959 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  "Report to National -Policy and Program Committee, " "Analysis of Activities of Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism," leaflets.
- Jewish Labor Committee, Anti-Discrimination, 1949-1958 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  I.c.w. Emanuel Muravchik.
- Jewish Labor Committee, Civil Rights, 1946-1958 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Incl. speeches by CSZ, memoranda, news releases. Outlook.
- Jobber-Contractor Dept., 1944-1956 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Annual reports.
- Jobber-Contractor Dept., 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Incl. memorandum re Sherman Anti-Trust Law.
- Jurisdictional Disputes, Intra-Union, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Incl. correspondence. & reports re Jerry Gilden (firm); report of GEB Special Committee on Jurisdiction.
- Jurisdictional Disputes, Intra-Union, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Incl. list of shops controlled by Local 105.
- Jurisdictional Disputes, Intra-Union, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Incl. correspondence. & reports re disputes w. Local 25.
- Jurisdictional Disputes, Intra-Union, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  I.c.w. Local 25.
- Jurisdictional Disputes, Intra-Union, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Disputes involving Baker Bros., Chicladee Dress & Monart Dress Mfg. Co.
- Jurisdictional Disputes, Intra-Union, 1936-1947 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  I.c.w. N.Y. Cloak Jt. Bd. & Local 25.
- King, Martin L., Jr., 1958-1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Corres. w. M.L. King, CSZ telegrams protesting arrests & treatment of King & other blacks.
- L, 1958-1964 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  Incl. ltr. from Herbert h. Lehman.
- Labor Day Parades, 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Legislation, 1959-1963 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Legislation, 1959-1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Local Managers, 1958-1961 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Minutes.
- Local 102, 1941-1955 (Box 14, Folder 3a)
  Memorandum "in the matter of the complaint of the Jt. Bd... against Local 102 before a committee of the GEB of the ILGWU" (1941); judgment against Garment Truckmen of N.J., Inc., et al (Oct. 4, 1955).
- Locals 10,22,60,89, 1947-1954 (Box 14, Folder 3b)
  Incl. correspondence., leaflets, programs; tributes (50th anniversary of Local 10) by JH, Luigi Antonini, William Green; report of 1953 Examination, Objection & Election Comm. of Local 89; report of Special Investigation Comm. of Local 89 re Salvatore Flocker.
- Locals, N.Y.C. [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1956 (Box 14, Folder 4a)
  incl. Report (1950) of Local 91, by-laws of Vacation Fund of Undergarment & Negligee Workers' Union, Local 62; election leaflets for Locals 9,35,66 and 55.
- Locals, N.Y.C. [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1956 (Box 14, Folder 4b)
- Out-of-Town Locals and Jt. Bds. [folder 1 of 2], 1957-1964 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  I.c.w. Angela Bambace, Morris Bialis, Salvatore Ninfo, Bernard Shane, Frederick Siems, Cornelius Wall; incl. text of Silk Dress Agreement of Phila. Dress Jt. Bd.
- Out-of-Town Locals and Jt. Bds. [folder 2 of 2], 1957-1964 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Out-of-Town Locals and Jt. Bds. [folder 1 of 2], 1944-1954 (Box 14, Folder 7a)
  I.c.w. Abraham Plotkin & re Forest City Mfg. Co.; summary of Local 49 history; text of Justice clippings (1919) re Chicago Jt. Bd.; report of Pacific Coast Region by Louis Levy (1945).
- Out-of-Town Locals and Jt. Bds. [folder 2 of 2], 1944-1954 (Box 14, Folder 7b)
- Lombardy Dress Co., 1945-1949 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Incl. ltrs. from Sidney Blauner re non-union firms.
- Los Angeles Cloak and Dress Joint Board, 1946-1957 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  I.c.w. Isidore Stenzor; memos & reports re conflict w. Samuel Otto.
- L.A. Cloak and Dress Jt. Bd., 1950-1956 (Box 15, Folder 1a)
  Incl. notices, ballots, lists of candidates, leaflets of election in L.A. Dress Jt. Bd.
- L.A. Cloak and Dress Jt. Bd., 1950-1954 (Box 15, Folder 1b)
  Newspaper clippings concerning reorganization of Jt. Bd.; incl. Thru the Needle's Eve (2 issues) & Report to the Members 1947-50.
- L.A. Cloak and Dress Jt. Bd., 1950-1952 (Box 15, Folder 1c)
  I.c.w. Fannie Borax, Isidore Stenzor; correspondence., reports, resolution of 27th Convention of Union re reorganization of Jt. Bd.
- L.A. Cloak and Dress Jt. Bd., 1950 (Box 15, Folder 1d)
  August 1950. Majority & minority reports of GEB Committee to reorganize Jt. Bd. incl. notes on controversy w. Meyer Perlstein.
- Lurye, William, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Incl. chronology of events re Lurye murder & attack on Bill Ross; correspondence. w. district attorney.
- M, 1947-1958 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. James Middleton.
- Madison Square Garden Meeting, 1932-1933 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Concert & Celebration of Jt. Bd.; incl. speeches by JH & William Green.
- Membership, 1939-1953 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Membership figures of Locals 10,22,60,89.
- Men Awake!, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 6a)
  Copy of song by Harold J. Rome, autographed by N.Y. & Out-of-Town ILGWU Choruses, presented to JH.
- Miscellaneous, 1963-1965 (Box 15, Folder 6b)
  Incl. expressions (anonymous) of criticism of Union positions on Vietnam war.
- N, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Minutes, Executive Committee, N.Y. Dress Institute? N.Y.S. AFL-CIO.
- National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1964 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Cases, incl. Blue Gem Dress Co.,& Susan Evans, Inc.
- National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1964 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- NLRB, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Decisions involving Penna. shops.
- NLRB, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Negotiations, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Negotiations, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  February 1973.
- Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Incl. basic facts of proposed agreement.
- Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  I.c.w. N.Y. State Mediation Board.
- Negotiations, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Incl. memo from Stuart Linnick re "Fashion Capital of the World."
- Negotiations, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  I.c.w. Pay Board (U.S.).
- Negotiations, 1949-1972 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  Incl. arbitrator's award against Eddy Modes, Inc.
- Negotiations, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Incl. leaflets of Independent Cutters Club.
- Negotiations, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  Rank and File leaflets.
- Negotiations, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Dec. 1969-Jan. 1970.
- Negotiations, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Negotiations, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Negotiations, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Incl. leaflets (2) of "independent" members.
- Negotiations, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Negotiations, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Oct. 1966-Nov. 1967. Index & history of 1967 negotiations.
- Negotiations, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  Dec. 1966-Jan. 1967.
- Negotiations, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Incl. Progressive Labor Party leaflet.
- Negotiations, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Negotiations, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Negotiations, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Negotiations, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Negotiations, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Incl. statements by CSZ & Association managers & directors at first industry conference, Dec. 12, 1963.
- Negotiations, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Negotiations, 1961-1963 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Negotiations, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Negotiations, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Negotiations, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Feb. 1961.
- Negotiations, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Dec. 1960-Nov. 1961. I.c.w. NYC Fire Dept. re Fire Warden Program.
- Negotiations, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Nov. 1960-June 1961. Index and history.
- Negotiations, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  Nov. 1960-Feb. 1961.
- Negotiations, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  April 1960-Jan. 1961.
- Negotiations, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Feb. 1960-Jan. 1961.
- Negotiations, 1950-1959 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Negotiations, 1955-1959 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Incl. Wilbur Daniels memo re picket line incidents.
- Negotiations, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Jan. 1958-Mar. 1959. Incl. notes on conference bet. JH, Emil Schlesinger & Lazare Teper.
- Negotiations, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Index and history.
- Negotiations, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Aug. 1957-Dec. 1958.
- Negotiations, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  Oct. 1957-Sept. 1958.
- Negotiations, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  Sept. 1957-June 1958.
- Negotiations, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  Mar. 1957-June 1958.
- Negotiations, 1953-1959 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  Incl. report of Special Trial Committee of GEB re Harry Schindler & Edward Spritzer (Sept. 1, 1959); David Dubinsky ltr. reprimanding Max Bluestein (Jan. 13, 1955); JH memo re "General Conditions in Industry, Fall Season 1953."
- Negotiations, 1951-1958 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Negotiations, 1951-1958 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Negotiations, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Negotiations, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Negotiations, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Negotiations, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Negotiations, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Negotiations, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  Incl. Federal Mediation and Conciliation Services' announcement of labor dispute.
- Negotiations, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Negotiations, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  Feb. 14, 1955. Dr. Lazare Teper memo.
- Negotiations, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Negotiations, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Negotiations, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Negotiations, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 16)